Guide to the Anaconda Copper Mining Company records 1876-1974
Montana Historical Society
- General Office
  - Subject Files [General Office, Anaconda]
    - #93, #537 Audits: Montana Lumber and Manufacturing Company, Northern Coal Company, Northwest Coal Company, Pacific Lumber Company, 1899-1900 (Box-folder 51 / 2)
    - #93, #537 Audits: Mountain Trading Company, 1901-1910 (Box-folder 51 / 3)
    - #93, #537 Audits: Purchasing Department, 1899 (Box-folder 51 / 4)
    - #93, #537 Audits: Washoe Copper Company/Coke Department, Storrs; Coal Department, Bear Creek, 1904-1911 (Box-folder 51 / 5)
    - #94 "Inventory of California House...", 1900-1901 (Box-folder 51 / 6)
    - #95 Mines payroll, 1900-1905 (Box-folder 51 / 7)
    - #98 Net proceeds of mines tax, 1900 (Box-folder 51 / 8)
    - #101 Census report on Reduction Works, 1899 (Box-folder 51 / 9)
    - #102 "Lumber used at Anaconda Co. and Washoe Co. mines", 1900 (Box-folder 51 / 10)
    - #105 "Settlements for custom ore and custom matte", 1900 (Box-folder 51 / 11)
    - #108 Casualty insurance, 1899-1904 (Box-folder 51 / 12)
    - #113 Boarding houses at Carroll, 1897-1900 (Box-folder 51 / 13)
    - #114 "Cost of Logs at Hamilton", 1899-1901 (Box-folder 51 / 14)
    - #116 F.P. Brayton report on lumber plants at Bonner, St. Regis, and Hamilton, 1900 (Box-folder 51 / 15)
    - #118 "Analysis of Carbon Coal", 1900 (Box-folder 51 / 16)
    - #119 "Statement showing amount due Washoe Copper Company for concentrating ore received from the Pacific Lode", 1899-1900 (Box-folder 51 / 17)
    - #120 Columbia Falls ground lease, 1899 (Box-folder 51 / 18)
    - #121 "Claim of M.H. McNulty for additional recompense for ore taken from Big Modoc Mine", 1899-1900 (Box-folder 51 / 19)
    - #122 M.R. Perry report on Foundry Department, 1900 (Box-folder 51 / 20)
    - #123 "Inventory of Boarding House below Carroll", 1894-1904 (Box-folder 51 / 21)
    - #124 "Coal Land Declaratory Statement blanks", 1900-1901 (Box-folder 51 / 22)
    - #126 "Stationery, Printing and Blank Books purchased from Standard Publishing Company", 1900-1901 (Box-folder 51 / 23)
    - #134 "Inventory of property in General Office and Legal Department Butte", 1901 (Box-folder 51 / 24)
    - #135 "Foundry Department depreciation...", 1900 (Box-folder 51 / 25)
    - #139 "Contract of A.J. Holmes and Co., with Copper City Com. Co.", 1892 (Box-folder 51 / 26)
    - #140 "Claim and Release of James S. Doyle (re injury at Anaconda smelter), 1897 (Box-folder 51 / 27)
    - #141 Sales between departments, 1900 (Box-folder 51 / 28)
    - #143 "Inventory of stock and property in Company Stables" (re horses), 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 1)
    - #144 "Statement of Coal used at Mines", 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 2)
    - #146 "Bills against B.A. and P. Ry bill for services of linemen" (re Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway), 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 3)
    - #148 "Bonds on issue of duplicate paychecks", 1905 (Box-folder 52 / 4)
    - #149 "Expenses of Sampling Works, Butte", 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 5)
    - #151 "Comparative analyses of Diamondville, Belt, Red Lodge, and Rock Springs coal", 1897-1899 (Box-folder 52 / 6)
    - #152 Memoranda of agreements: Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway and Anaconda Standard (re telegraph lines), 1895 (Box-folder 52 / 7)
    - #155 "Index to construction order numbers New Reduction Works", 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 8)
    - #156 Margaret Theater Association (re foreclosure sale), 1909 (Box-folder 52 / 9)
    - #157 "Cost of equipping Reverberatory Furnace #7 Lower Works with Boiler attachment", 1900 (Box-folder 52 / 10)
    - #159 "Detail of cost of Refinery Building #3", 1900 (Box-folder 52 / 11)
    - #160 "Bear Creek coal filings", 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 12)
    - #167 Royalties on Monitor ore, 1899 (Box-folder 52 / 13)
    - #172 Contract: Butte, Anaconda, and Pacific Railway and Western Union Telegraph Company, 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 14)
    - #174 Income and expenditure estimates: Big Blackfoot Milling Company, Diamond Coal and Coke Company, Mountain Trading Company, and Washoe Copper Company, 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 15)
    - #175 Coal used at Reduction Works, 1896-1901 (Box-folder 52 / 16)
    - #176 Reports of operation and production: Reduction Works, 1895-1896 (Box-folder 52 / 17)
    - #177 "Contract with H. Thofehrn and plans for Electrolytic Refinery at Anaconda", 1893-1894 (Box-folder 52 / 18)
    - #178 Wood settlement: Anaconda Fluming Company, 1896 (Box-folder 52 / 19)
    - #180 Accounts receivable: Lumber Department, Butte, 1898-1904 (Box-folder 52 / 20)
    - #188 "Settlement for silver slimes shipped to Seattle Smelting & Refining Co.", 1902 (Box-folder 52 / 21)
    - #190 "Sales, Cost, and Profit statements", 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 22)
    - #191 "Mining costs", 1898-1903 (Box-folder 52 / 23)
    - #192 "Contracts with Rocky Mountain Bell Telephone Co.", 1902 (Box-folder 52 / 24)
    - #193 Sales between departments, 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 25)
    - #195 "Log account Lumber Dept., Hamilton", 1901 (Box-folder 52 / 26)
    - #196 "Miscellaneous papers taken from desks in Mr. Daly's office", 1893-1900 (Box-folder 52 / 27)
    - #201 Bad debts and depreciation (all departments), 1902 (Box-folder 52 / 28)
    - #205 Net proceeds of mines tax, 1902 (Box-folder 52 / 29)
    - #206 Contracts: Lumber Department, Hamilton, 1900 (Box-folder 52 / 30)
    - #211 Wages paid and hours worked at New Reduction Works; salaries of officers and foremen, 1902-1903 (Box-folder 52 / 31)
    - #212 "Settlement for silver slimes shipped to American Smelting and Refining Company, Omaha", 1902-1903 (Box-folder 52 / 32)
    - #213 "Statements of amounts paid on account of personal injury claims", 1897-1901, 1904 (Box-folder 52 / 33)
    - #214 Henry Prentiss report re dismantling of Upper Works, 1902 (Box-folder 53 / 1)
    - #215 "Inventory of Office Furniture and Laboratory Supplies and Utensils moved from Old Works to New Works", undated (Box-folder 53 / 2)
    - #216 "Statement of Operating Expenses of Butte Mines Machine Shop", 1902 (Box-folder 53 / 3)
    - #217 "Monthly statement of tons of ore extracted from A.C.M. Co. mines", 1902-1903 (Box-folder 53 / 4)
    - #219 "Cupreous Material received and Cast Copper produced at New Reduction Works", 1902 (Box-folder 53 / 5)
    - #220 "Copies of insurance riders", 1905 (Box-folder 53 / 6)
    - #221 Internal revenue stamps, 1901 (Box-folder 53 / 7)
    - #222 "Expenditures on account of the construction of the New Reduction Works", 1902 (Box-folder 53 / 8)
    - #223 "Machinery, material and supplies taken from the Old Reduction Works and used in New Reduction Works construction", 1901-1902 (Box-folder 53 / 9)
    - #224 "Machinery, material and supplies taken from the Old Reduction Works and used in New Reduction Works operations", 1902 (Box-folder 53 / 10)
    - #225 "Cost of New Reduction Works buildings and equipment...", 1902 (Box-folder 53 / 11)
    - #226 "Monthly report of Construction at Butte mines", 1902-1903 (Box-folder 53 / 12)
    - #227 "Monthly report of cost of special work at Butte mines...", 1902-1903 (Box-folder 53 / 13)
    - #228 "Average cost of making Fire Brick", 1902 (Box-folder 53 / 14)
    - #229 "Lumber used at the Mines...in Butte", 1901-1904 (Box-folder 53 / 15)
    - #230 "Coal used at Mines", 1901-1902 (Box-folder 53 / 16)
    - #233 "Various labor charges to New Works Construction by Old Reduction Works", 1901-1902 (Box-folder 53 / 17)
    - #234 Statements of operations, 1902-1904 (Box-folder 53 / 18)
    - #235 "List of employees at New Reduction Works", 1902 December (Box-folder 53 / 19)
    - #237 Reconciliation of Reduction Works and mine operating expenses, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 53 / 20)
    - #238 "Cupreous material on hand at New Reduction Works", 1903-1904 (Box-folder 53 / 21)
    - #239 Operating costs of New Reduction Works, 1902 (Box-folder 53 / 22)
    - #240 U.S. Census statements, 1902, 1907 (Box-folder 54 / 1)
    - #241 "Assessment work done on mining claims in Silver Bow County", 1902 (Box-folder 54 / 2)
    - #242 "Mines payrolls by days and occupations", 1902 (Box-folder 54 / 3)
    - #244 "Silver Slimes from Great Falls cost of treating at Silver Mill", 1903 (Box-folder 54 / 4)
    - #246 "Charges to sundry mining claims", 1900 (Box-folder 54 / 5)
    - #250 "Relief to Smelter Power House a/c steam supplied by Reverberatory Boilers", 1903-1905 (Box-folder 54 / 6)
    - #251 Statements re census figures, 1902 (Box-folder 54 / 7)
    - #271 "Ore received from all Mines", 1895-1898 (Box-folder 54 / 8)
    - #272 "Report of Production, Operations, Costs, and Shipments, Old Works", 1895 (Box-folder 54 / 9)
    - #279 Custom ore profits, 1896-1897 (Box-folder 54 / 10)
    - #280 Copper and bullion shipments, 1895 (Box-folder 54 / 11)
    - #282-283 Custom ore purchases, 1897 (Box-folder 54 / 12-13)
    - #286 "Cost of producing copper", 1898-1899 (Box-folder 54 / 14)
    - #287 "Syndicate Mines reports", 1894-1895 (Box-folder 54 / 15)
    - #290 "Matte shipments from C.S. and M. Co." (re Colorado Smelting and Mining Company), 1899 (Box-folder 54 / 16)
    - #292 Losses in smelting and concentrating, 1894-1898 (Box-folder 54 / 17)
    - #293 "Payments made by Marcus Daly to Henry Burrell for investigation and purchase of coal lands", 1897 (Box-folder 54 / 18)
    - #296 "Contract for Upper Works flume", 1897 (Box-folder 54 / 19)
    - #297 "Costs and Operations", 1897 (Box-folder 54 / 20)
    - #298 "Comparative test of Belt and Diamond coals", 1898 (Box-folder 54 / 21)
    - #299 "Report of operations", 1897 (Box-folder 54 / 22)
    - #300 "Report of John S. Dougherty to Marcus Daly [re] Improvements & Land Purchases", 1892-1894 (Box-folder 54 / 23)
    - #301 Average costs of mining and smelting, 1894 (Box-folder 54 / 24)
    - #302 Mining and reduction expenses; tons mined; custom ore, 1894 (Box-folder 54 / 25)
    - #309 Quarterly report: departments, 1895 September (Box-folder 54 / 26)
    - #310 Casting reports, 1897 (Box-folder 54 / 27)
    - #311 Cost of producing matte: Upper and Lower Works, 1896 (Box-folder 54 / 28)
    - #312 "Detail of cupreous material on hand", 1902-1902 (Box-folder 54 / 29)
    - #313 "Report of Melting", 1896 (Box-folder 54 / 30)
    - #314 "Freight settlements", 1892-1895 (Box-folder 54 / 31)
    - #317 "Monthly Mine Reports operation & production" [sampled], 1893 (Box-folder 54 / 32)
    - #318 Inventory of boarding house #3, 1899 (Box-folder 54 / 33)
    - #319 "Detail of expenses", 1902 (Box-folder 54 / 34)
    - #321 Butte Mines Machine Shop expenses, etc., 1903 (Box-folder 54 / 35)
    - #322 "Statements of Coal and Lumber Rec'd at the Butte mines", 1903-1904 (Box-folder 54 / 36)
    - #323 "Mines payrolls" (summaries only), 1903-1906 (Box-folder 55 / 1)
    - #329 "Silver Slimes purchased", 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 2)
    - #330 New Works construction, 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 3)
    - #334 Mines and Reduction Works operating costs, 1902-1903 (Box-folder 55 / 4)
    - #337 Bad debts and depreciation (all departments), 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 5)
    - #338 Construction order #3: New Reduction Works, 1900-1902 (Box-folder 55 / 6)
    - #339 Cathode copper shipments to Baltimore, 1900 (Box-folder 55 / 7)
    - #341 Cost of analytic tests made at Laboratory, 1905 (Box-folder 55 / 8)
    - #342 Construction order #260 (re dismantlement of old converter building), 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 9)
    - #344 "Names and addresses of clerks in General Office", 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 10)
    - #345 Inventory: Silver Lake Pumping Station, 1900-1903 (Box-folder 55 / 11)
    - #346 Sales between departments, 1902 (Box-folder 55 / 12)
    - #351 "Detail of charges to New Stack and Flues", 1903-1904 (Box-folder 55 / 13)
    - #352 "Book Cost of Briquetting and Brick Plants", 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 14)
    - #353 "Scales taken from Blast Furnace & placed in E. Anaconda" (re construction order 221a), 1901-1903 (Box-folder 55 / 15)
    - #356 "Depreciation curves", 1904 (Box-folder 55 / 16)
    - #357 "Gregson Springs Quarry on Monument Placer", 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 17)
    - #358 "Basis for various settlements for matte, ore, precipitates etc. purchased", undated (Box-folder 55 / 18)
    - #359 Census Office and U.S. Geological Survey forms, 1902, 1907 (Box-folder 55 / 19)
    - #361 "Analysis of Debits & Credits to Barn & Teaming Expense", 1902 (Box-folder 55 / 20)
    - #363 Macinac Mining Company lease, 1903-1904 (Box-folder 55 / 21)
    - #364 "Machinery & Tools on hand, Constr. of New Works, Flues & Stacks, C.O. 500", 1903, 1905 (Box-folder 55 / 22)
    - #365 Butte Mines Machine Shop expenses, etc., 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 23)
    - #366 "Construction Order #200A. Moving 16 Boilers from Upper Works to E.L. & Ry Upper power plant., 1902 (Box-folder 55 / 24)
    - #367 New Works concentrating tables, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 55 / 25)
    - #369 "Charges to New Works Construction", 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 26)
    - #370 "Coal Mining Cos. in United States", 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 27)
    - #371 "Cost of construction of Concentrator Power House and cost of output", 1902-1903 (Box-folder 55 / 28)
    - #372 "Formula for producing a black color on brass", undated (Box-folder 55 / 29)
    - #373 "Basis of distribution of Rental to Plants", 1902 (Box-folder 55 / 30)
    - #374 "Burned Lime from Brown's Quarry", 1904 (Box-folder 55 / 31)
    - #377 Parrot Silver and Copper Company account (re Bellona ore), 1903-1905 (Box-folder 55 / 32)
    - #378 "Company's telephones in Anaconda & Butte", 1904 (Box-folder 55 / 33)
    - #379 "Vincent Ranch" (re lime and silica quarry), 1903 (Box-folder 55 / 34)
    - #380 "Miscellaneous enclosures to New York office", 1900-1904 (Box-folder 56 / 1)
    - #388 Royalties, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 56 / 2)
    - #389 "Cupreous material received to New Works and cast copper produced", 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 3)
    - #391 "Cost, Depreciation and Book value Mercantile Depts & Mountain Trading Co.", 1903 (Box-folder 56 / 4)
    - #393 Inventory of motors at New Works, 1903 (Box-folder 56 / 5)
    - #394 "Laboratory expense", 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 6)
    - #395 Deed: Butte Electric Railway Company, 1902 (Box-folder 56 / 7)
    - #397 "Mines machinery warehouse Butte, Mont. Detail of cost of construction", 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 8)
    - #398 "Distribution of plant & equipment", 1903-1904 (Box-folder 56 / 9)
    - #399 "Operations at Reduction Works", 1903 (Box-folder 56 / 10)
    - #400 "Ore extracted from Ground Squirrel Mine", 1895-1896 (Box-folder 56 / 11)
    - #401 "Ore from Leasers", 1904-1905 (Box-folder 56 / 12)
    - #403 "Lease of Anaconda Copper Mining Company's water rights in Deer Lodge County to Washoe Copper Company", 1902 (Box-folder 56 / 13)
    - #404 "Agreement for operation of New Works between the Washoe Copper Company and the Anaconda Copper Mining Company", 1902 (Box-folder 56 / 14)
    - #405 Net proceeds of mines tax, 1903-1904 (Box-folder 56 / 15)
    - #409 "List of operations as shown on cost sheet", undated (Box-folder 56 / 16)
    - #410 Garnishments at Mine Office, 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 17)
    - #411 "Total charges to construction of New Reduction Works", 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 18)
    - #412 "Comparative statement of office clerks...with salaries paid", 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 19)
    - #413 Ground Squirrel and Camp Creek accounts, 1896-1898 (Box-folder 56 / 20)
    - #414 "Cost of construction of High Ore Pumping Plant", 1901-1903 (Box-folder 56 / 21)
    - #415 U.S. Geological Survey forms, 1903-1904 (Box-folder 56 / 22)
    - #416 "Machinery and Material from Camp Creek Mines, sent to Butte warehouse", 1896 (Box-folder 56 / 23)
    - #417 "Memorandums regarding division of Works Expenses, method followed, etc.", 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 24)
    - #420 New Reduction Works operating costs, 1903 (Box-folder 56 / 25)
    - #421 Butte Mines Machine Shop expenses, 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 26)
    - #422 "Frank Brown Placer Mining Claim", 1899 (Box-folder 56 / 27)
    - #430 "Distribution of royalty collected on High Ore precipitates", 1903 (Box-folder 56 / 28)
    - #432 Inventory of cupreous material at New Works, 1904-1906 (Box-folder 56 / 29)
    - #433 "Ore mined and shipped to Anaconda", 1904-1905 (Box-folder 56 / 30)
    - #435 New Works construction reconciliations, 1902-1909 (Box-folder 56 / 31)
    - #436 Taxes, 1898-1902 (Box-folder 56 / 32)
    - #437 "New Reduction Works cost and rental", 1902-1909 (Box-folder 56 / 33)
    - #438 Fire clay and silica bricks, undated (Box-folder 56 / 34)
    - #439 "Classes of labor at New Reduction Works", 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 35)
    - #440 Reduction Works expenses, 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 36)
    - #441 "Smelter group, construction costs", 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 37)
    - #442 "Charges to New Reduction Works construction", 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 38)
    - #445 "Purchased and lease ores received at Anaconda for B. & B. Con. Mng. Co." [Butte and Boston], 1904-1905 (Box-folder 56 / 39)
    - #446 Reduction works expenses and production, 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 40)
    - #450 Margaret Theater receipts and expenditures, 1904 (Box-folder 56 / 41)
    - #452 "Meeting re shop order account and New works accounts", 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 1)
    - #453 Lulu Placer Mining claim, 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 2)
    - #454 Boston and Montana Consolidated Copper and Silver Mining Company coal account, 1901 (Box-folder 57 / 3)
    - #455 Royalties on iron ore and lime rock from Morrill Quarry, 1901-1904 (Box-folder 57 / 4)
    - #457 Payments to Pogson, Peloubet and Company (auditors), 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 5)
    - #458 Copper produced, 1901 (Box-folder 57 / 6)
    - #460 Taxes, 1897 (Box-folder 57 / 7)
    - #461 Three Forks property, 1900-1901 (Box-folder 57 / 8)
    - #465 Mines operating expenses, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 57 / 9)
    - #466 "List of dwelling houses in Deer Lodge County owned by the Washoe Copper Company", 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 10)
    - #467 Frank Klepetko's appointment as manager, 1900 (Box-folder 57 / 11)
    - #468 Big Blackfoot Milling Company agency accounts, 1901 (Box-folder 57 / 12)
    - #469 "Cost of mining timbers received at Butte Mines", 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 13)
    - #470 New Reduction Works operating accounts, undated (Box-folder 57 / 14)
    - #473 "Monthly construction statements, Electrolytic Refinery at Anaconda", 1895 (Box-folder 57 / 15)
    - #474 Electrolytic Refinery at Anaconda, 1895 (Box-folder 57 / 16)
    - #475 Lost Creek ditch costs, 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 17)
    - #476 Division of veterinarian's salary between departments, 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 18)
    - #477 Inventory of mechanical equipment at New Works, 1903 (Box-folder 57 / 19)
    - #478 Mines and Reduction Works construction, 1895 (Box-folder 57 / 20)
    - #479 Butte Mines repair expenses, 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 21)
    - #480 Expense of auditing company's accounts, 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 22)
    - #482 Report on Reduction Works to Dept. of Commerce, 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 23)
    - #483 "Basis of treating one ton of Reverberatory slag in Blast Furnaces", 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 24)
    - #484 "Converter Plant: matte storage furnaces and equipment", 1901-1902 (Box-folder 57 / 25)
    - #485 Cost of Electric Plant at Refinery, 1901-1902 (Box-folder 57 / 26)
    - #486 Taylor and Brunton settlement sheets [assays], 1903-1904 (Box-folder 57 / 27)
    - #489 "Lease of Mountain View Park to Butte, Anaconda, and Pacific Railway", 1899 (Box-folder 57 / 28)
    - #499 "Royalties credited to Washoe Copper Co.", 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 29)
    - #503 "Construction order #14: Machine Shop equipment", 1900-1903 (Box-folder 57 / 30)
    - #508 New Works Carpenter shop equipment, 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 31)
    - #509 New Works Boiler shop equipment, 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 32)
    - #510 New Works Pipe shop equipment, 1903 (Box-folder 57 / 33)
    - #511 New Works construction, 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 34)
    - #512 Local tramming costs, 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 35)
    - #514 Construction order #500 (re construction of New Reduction Works), 1903-1904 (Box-folder 57 / 36)
    - #516 Net proceeds of mines tax, 1905-1915 (Box-folder 57 / 37)
    - #520 List of employees: departments, 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 38)
    - #521 Marcus Daly Estate account, 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 39)
    - #522 Numbers of employees (by job and ethnic origin, 1881-1894) (Box-folder 57 / 40)
    - #523 Ore account, 1904 (Box-folder 57 / 41)
    - #531 New Works construction, 1905-1907 (Box-folder 57 / 42)
    - #533 Numbers of employees at Anaconda, 1901-1905 (Box-folder 57 / 43)
    - #534 Old Works general expense, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 57 / 44)
    - #535 Refinery and silver Mill expenses, 1902 (Box-folder 57 / 45)
    - #539 "Cost of construction of New Precipitating Plant at Old Works", 1905 (Box-folder 57 / 46)
    - #551 New Works incidental expenses, 1906 (Box-folder 57 / 47)
    - #552 New Works construction vouchers, 1905-1906 (Box-folder 57 / 48)
    - #553 "Valuation of Telephone System", 1906 (Box-folder 57 / 49)
    - #555 Net proceeds of mines tax, 1906 (Box-folder 57 / 50)
    - #557 Soldiers Additional Homestead Right claims, 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 1)
    - #558 Expense of auditing company's accounts, 1905 (Box-folder 58 / 2)
    - #559 Insurance premiums, 1901-1906 (Box-folder 58 / 3)
    - #561 Montana Water, Electric Power and Mining Company v. Mary Schuh, et al. decree of court re water rights, 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 4)
    - #563 Deed: Nipper lode claim, 1896 (Box-folder 58 / 5)
    - #564 Inventories (includes buildings, machinery, and supplies at Butte mines), 1895-1896 (Box-folder 58 / 6)
    - #565 "Mtn Con Office construction reports" (re Mountain Consolidated, Green Mountain, and Bell mines), 1895-1896 (Box-folder 58 / 7)
    - #567 "Smelter Power House distribution of expenses", 1905 (Box-folder 58 / 8)
    - #568 "Copy of Montana Code provisions concerning assessment of net proceeds of mines", undated (Box-folder 58 / 9)
    - #570 Construction order #500 inventory (re New Reduction Works construction), 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 10)
    - #571 St. Lawrence change house repair, 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 11)
    - #572 "Inventory of ranch near Darby, Montana", 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 12)
    - #573 "Value of cupreous material on hand", 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 13)
    - #574 "Butte & Boston Consolidated Mining Company ore received at Reduction Works", 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 14)
    - #576 Bad debts and depreciation, 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 15)
    - #578 Taxes, 1902-1905 (Box-folder 58 / 16)
    - #582 "Cost to treat Blast & Converter flue dust at Reverberatory", 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 17)
    - #583 "Tax papers and lists" (by county and in Butte), 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 18)
    - #585 Construction expenses, 1906-1908 (Box-folder 58 / 19)
    - #586 "Expenditures on closed construction orders compared with appropriations", 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 20)
    - #587 "Indian Queen ore statements", 1905-1906 (Box-folder 58 / 21)
    - #590 "Expenditures on placer claims at Maiden Rock" (re limestone), 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 22)
    - #592 Webbs Quarry inventory, 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 23)
    - #595 Bacteriological Laboratory inventory, 1907, 1909 (Box-folder 58 / 24)
    - #598 Classification of labor at Reduction Works, 1906 (Box-folder 58 / 25)
    - #599 Cupreous material inventories, 1906-1908 (Box-folder 58 / 26)
    - #601 Montana Water, Electric Power, and Mining Company and Flint Creek power plant costs, 1906-1909 (Box-folder 58 / 27)
    - #602 New Works mechanical equipment inventory, 1907, 1910 (Box-folder 58 / 28)
    - #603 Bernard Falk liability release (re New Works flume overflow), 1905 (Box-folder 58 / 29)
    - #604 J.R. Gibson account (re loading Old Works slums, etc.), 1903-1904 (Box-folder 59 / 1)
    - #605 Theodore Hennessy account (re team hire for New Works flue and stack construction), 1903 (Box-folder 59 / 2)
    - #606 "Bellona ore mined through Moonlight shaft", 1903 (Box-folder 59 / 3)